Q: What is the output of `print(2 ** 3)` in Python?
Ans: Option B

Q: How do you calculate the remainder of 10 divided by 3 in Python?
Ans: Option C

Q: Which Python keyword is used to start a loop that repeats as long as a condition is true?
Ans: Option D

Q: What happens if you don't increment the counter in a while loop?
Ans: Option B

Q: Which of the following is a mutable data structure in Python?
Ans: Option C

Q: How do you access the first element in a Python list named `my_list`?
Ans: Option B

